{
    "subject": "resource/Angel_Blue",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "American opera singer",
    "human_readable": "Angel Blue's short description is an American opera singer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7717893719673157,
            "question": "What type of singer is Angel Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45049160718917847,
            "question": "What are some of Angel Blue's most famous opera roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42689698934555054,
            "question": "What nationality is Angel Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4138115346431732,
            "question": "Is Angel Blue known for performing classical music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41053450107574463,
            "question": "What is Angel Blue known for musically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4010790288448334,
            "question": "Does Angel Blue perform with any particular opera companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33672988414764404,
            "question": "Where is Angel Blue from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3341265022754669,
            "question": "Has Angel Blue performed in any notable productions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24239353835582733,
            "question": "Has Angel Blue won any awards for her singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1824941188097,
            "question": "What musical training did Angel Blue receive?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Angel Blue's short description is an American opera singer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1903_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Angel Blue won any awards for her singing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1903_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Angel Blue performed in any notable productions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1903_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Angel Blue from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1903_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1903_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe context information mentions that Angel Blue is a classical and operatic music singer, but it does not mention that she sings opera. It actually says \"American classical and opera singer\" which implies that her main genre of singing is classical music, with some work in opera."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided describe Angel Blue as an American classical and opera singer, which supports the statement that her \"short description is an American opera singer.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the context information provided describes Angel Blue as a classical singer-songwriter who has performed in operatic music, not just an opera singer.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}